Guide to the George P. Garrett Papers, 1929-2008 (bulk 1960-2000)
George P. Garrett papers 1929-2008 (bulk 1960-2000)
- Audiovisual Material Series, 1970-1996 and undated
  - Garrett's Classes, Readings, Speeches, Workshops, and Lectures
    - Garrett/Gallery, 1986, Sept. 28, (3 tapes)
    - Garrett: reading Crowfoot and his autobiography, 1986, Oct. 7, (1 tape)
    - Garrett/Greensboro, 1986, Oct. 7, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett at Farmville, 1986, Oct. 16, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Williams Corner, 1986, Nov. 19, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett at Chapel Hill. 1987, Feb. 3, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at UMass, 1987, Feb. 19, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at George Mason, 1987, June 2, (1 tape)
    - Garrett/George Mason University, 1987, June 12, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett at Harvard, 1987, July 28, and at Aspen, 1987, Aug. 8, (1 tape)
    - Garrett/Bennington, 1987, July, and Aspen, 1987, Aug. 8, (1 tape)
    - Garrett/Aspen, 1987, Aug. 8, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett/Lecture, 1987, Aug., (1 tape)
    - Garrett/Poetry Society of VA, 1987, Sept. 19, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett/University of Tenn., 1987, Oct. 14, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett/Seminar at University of Tenn., 1987, Oct. 15, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett/University of Arkansas, 1987, Nov. 18, (3 tapes)
    - Garrett/Gallery, 1987, Dec. 6, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett at Jefferson Society, University of Virginia, 1988, Feb. 12, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett, 1988, Feb. 14, (1 tape)
    - Garrett, 1988, March 1, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett: Phi Beta Kappa, 1988, March 24, (3 tapes)
    - Clemson, 1988, Apr.18, (1 tape)
    - Garrett/Auburn, 1988, Apr. 19, (1 tape)
    - Garrett on Mary Lee Settle at Auburn University, 1988, Apr. 20, (4 tapes)
    - Garrett: Uncles, 1988, Apr. 21, (3 tapes)
    - Garrett at The Fortnightly Club, 1988, May 3, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: Interview by John Huber, 1988, May 16, (1 tape)
    - Garrett and Henry Taylor, 1988, July 20, (1 tape)
    - Garrett/Ole Miss on Faulkner, 1988, Aug. 5, (3 tapes)
    - Garrett at Aspen, 1988, Aug., (1 tape)
    - Garrett/Alabama, 1988, Sept. 29, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett/University of Virginia Fellows, 1988, Oct. 9, (1 tape)
    - Garrett, 1988, Nov. 17, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Sewanee, 1989, Jan. 23, (1 tape)
    - Garrett/NVCC, 1989, Feb. 21, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett, 1989, March 15, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at George Mason, 1989, March 27, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Southern University Conference, 1989, March 31, (1 tape)
    - Garrett/PSU, 1989, April 11, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett/Goucher College, 1989, April 17, (1 tape)
    - Garrett/ Under Two Flags, 1989, April 21, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at The Gallery, 1989, April 30, (1 tape)
    - Garrett, 1989, April 30, (1 tape)
    - Garrett, 1989, June 4, (1 tape)
    - Garrett on Weekend Edition, 1989, June 18, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Western Carolina University, 1989, Oct. 23-24, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Coker College, 1990, Feb. 6, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at NVCC, 1990, April 3, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: reading at Weber State University, 1990, April 13, (1 tape)
    - Garrett/Talk at Weber State University, 1990, April, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett: talk/reading/class, 1990, May 12-15, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: talk, 1990, May 15, and reading, 1990, May 28, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: talk, 1990, May 30, and reading, 1990, May 28, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett at Writers' Club, 1990, May 30, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Chapters Bookstore, 1990, Sept. 17, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett/reading and lecture at Florida International University (Miami), 1990, Sept. 20-21, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett at 2nd Street Gallery, 1990, Sept. 23, (2 tapes) (Box AV 3)
    - Garrett at University of S. Carolina, 1990, Sept. 27, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: readings, 1990, Sept. 27, and Oct. 4, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Hollins, 1990, Oct. 9, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: reading at Southern Seminar, 1990 Oct. 11, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at EWU, 1990, Oct. 19, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Virginia Military Institute, 1990, Dec. 4, (1 tape)
    - Garrett/Pen-Malamud Award, 1990, Dec. 7, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett at Farmington, 1991, Jan. 10, (1 tape)
    - Garrett/Greensboro, 1991, Feb. 5, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett/Hillsdale, 1991, Feb. 14, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett at Jefferson Society, 1991, Mar. 2, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: reading to Faculty Wives Club at University of Virginia, 1991, April 1, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: reading to teachers, 1991, April 24, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Florida Historical Society, 1991, May 10, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at University of Cincinnati, 1991, May 16-17, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: reading in Winchester, Va., 1991, Sept. 11, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at USC, 1991, Oct. 30, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Christopher Newport College, 1991, Nov. 6, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Large, 1991, Nov. 23, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: reading at Emory University, 1992 Feb. 18, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: The Lost Brother..., 1992, March 6, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: Memory, 1992, Sept. 23, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at F.Scott Fitzgerald Conf., 1992, Sept. 25, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett at Sewanee Review Banquet, 1992, Nov. 7, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: speech at Sewanee, 1992, Nov. 8, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at South Atlantic Modern Language Association, 1992, Nov. 13, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: reading to American Association of University Women, 1992, Nov. 21, and to Jefferson Scholars, 1992, Nov. 22, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett: reading to American Association of University Women, 1992, Nov. 22, and at 2nd Street Gallery, 1992, Dec. 6, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: reading at 2nd Street Gallery, 1992, Dec. 6, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett, 1993, May 12, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Alabama Symposium, 1993, Oct. 7, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Wisconsin, 1993, Oct. 20-21, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: reading to Alumni Associates, 1993, Dec. 8, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: Hong Kong radio interview, 1993, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Virginia Military Institute, 1994, Mar. 8, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: reading at Borders Bookstore, 1994, May 3, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at University of Virginia Alumni reunion, 1994, June 4, (1 tape)
    - Garrett, 1994, Sept. 22, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Montevallo, 1994, Sept. 28, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Montevallo, 1994, Nov. 2, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at University of Alabama-Huntsville, 1994, Nov. 9, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Sewanee, 1995, Jan. 23, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: reading at Williams Corner Bookstore, 1995, Feb. 1, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Saint Paul's, 1995, Feb. 26, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett: reading at the Rotunda, 1995, Mar. 17, (1 tape)
    - Garrett, 1995, March 29, (1 tape)
    - Garrett, 1995, April 21, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: reading from King of Babylon..., 1995, April 21 and 30, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: readings, 1995, April 30 and May 4, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Roger Williams, 1995, May 4, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Loudon County Library, 1995, May 11, (1 tape)
    - World War II, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett, undated, (4 tapes)
    - Garrett's movie class, undated, (4 tapes)
    - Garrett's class: Poison Pen, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Converse College, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at American University, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Stonecoast and Bennington, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Aspen, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Central Conn., undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Aspen and Bennington, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: reading, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett on the American novel, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at The Gallery, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: Under Two Flags, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: Poison Pen, undated, (3 tapes)
    - Garrett at Cincinnati, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Hollins, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: talk to Friends of Orlando Library, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Kiwanis in Richmond, Va., undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: readings, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at NVCC, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Weber State University, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Florida State University, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Penn State and University of Virginia, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Wesleyan, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: self-interview for Peden, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at University of New Hampshire, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at University of Michigan and at George Mason University, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Hollins, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett's last class at Wesleyan, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Alabama, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett at Johnson State College, undated, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett at University of North Dakota, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett: NPR interview and Folger party, undated, (2 tapes)
    - Garrett at George Mason University, undated, (1 tape)
    - Novel: 1910-1950, undated, (1 tape)
    - Garrett/Tandem, undated, (1 tape)
  - Lectures, Readings, and Presentations by Other Authors
    - Ardizzone, Tony: reading at Gallery, undated, (2 tapes) (Box AV 4)
    - Bausch/Hoagland, 1985, March 31, (1 tape)
    - Bausch/Greer, 1986, Nov. 16, (1 tape)
    - Bausch, Dick, undated, (1 tape)
    - Bausch, Robert, undated, (1 tape)
    - Bausch Brothers, 1986, March 23, (1 tape)
    - Bausch Brothers, 1988, March 27, (1 tape)
    - Bell, Madison, undated, (1 tape)
    - Benedict, Diane, 1984, July 19, (1 tape)
    - Benedict, Diane, undated, (1 tape)
    - Blythe et al., undated, (1 tape)
    - Boruch, Marianne, 1988, April 1, (1 tape)
    - Buechner reading, undated, (1 tape)
    - Chappell, Fred, 1985, July 2, (1 tape)
    - Chappell, Fred, 1987, Jan. 18, (1 tape)
    - Chappell Homecoming, 1988, May 30, (1 tape)
    - Chappell, Fred, 1988, July 2, (1 tape)
    - Chappell, Fred, 1992, Oct. 26, (3 tapes)
    - Chappell, Fred at Bent Mt., undated, (1 tape)
    - Chappell, Fred, undated, (1 tape)
    - Chappell/Taylor, undated, (1 tape)
    - Cheuse, Alan w. Carolyn Kizer at Bennington, 1984, July 4, (1 tape)
    - Cheuse, Alan, 1987, Feb. 1, (1 tape)
    - Chute, Carolyn w. Dennis Joltzen, 1984, July 16, (1 tape)
    - Chute, Carolyn, 1993, March 13, (2 tapes)
    - Ciardi, John at Duluth, undated, (1 tape)
    - Ciardi, John at NKU, undated, (1 tape)
    - Ciardi, John: Speaking of Words, undated, (1 tape)
    - Ciardi, John, undated, (1 tape)
    - de Colombi, Alicia: reading poems with Luis de Monguio, at Bennington, 1979, Dec. 6, (1 tape)
    - Conorer, Ted: reading, undated, (1 tape)
    - Conroy, Frank: Ploughshares, undated, (2 tapes)
    - Corman, Cid at Bennington, 1980, July 1, (1 tape)
    - Cox, James: Beneath My Father's Name, 1989, April 21, (1 tape)
    - Darntons at Bennington, 1982, July 29, (1 tape)
    - Davies, Robertson at Wesleyan, undated, (1 tape)
    - Day, Doug, 1988, May 1, (1 tape)
    - DelBanco, Nicholas at Michigan, 1984, March 28, (1 tape)
    - Dillard, R.H.W.: reading, early 1970s, (1 tape)
    - Dillard, R.H.W. at Folger Shakespeare Library, 1994, Oct. 25, (1 tape)
    - DiPiero, W.S. at Johnson State College, 1978, (3 tapes)
    - Dobyns, Stephen, 1983, July 21, (1 tape)
    - Dobyns, Stephen at Stonecoast, 1983, July, (1 tape)
    - Drake, Robert, 1983, Aug. 25, (1 tape)
    - Dubus, Andre at Stonecoast, 1981, July 14, (1 tape)
    - Dubus, Andre at Stonecoast, 1982, July 13, (1 tape)
    - Dubus, Andre, 1984, July 8, (1 tape)
    - Dubus, Andre at Stonecoast, undated, (1 tape)
    - Dunn, Stephen: lecture, undated, (1 tape)
    - Dunn, Stephen: reading, undated, (1 tape)
    - Dunning, Stephen, 1984, Jan. 24, (1 tape)
    - Ellison, Harlan at North Dakota, undated
    - Elman, Richard, 1984, July 3, (1 tape)
    - Elman, Richard, 1986, July 17, (1 tape)
    - Ford, Richard, 1986, July 14, (1 tape)
    - Fulton, Alice, 1986, Dec. 1, (2 tapes)
    - Galvin, Brendan at Michigan, 1984, April 10, (1 tape)
    - Galvin, Brendan, 1986, April 6, (2 tapes)
    - Galvin, Brendan at Folger Library, 1991, Oct. 28, (2 tapes)
    - Galvin, Brendan, undated, (3 tapes)
    - Giardina, Denise and Carolyn Chute at University of Virginia, 1985, March 6, (2 tapes)
    - Giardina and Chute at Hollins, 1985, March 7, (2 tapes)
    - Giardina and Chute at Hollins, undated, (1 tape)
    - Giardina and Chute, undated, (1 tape)
    - Giardina at University of Virginia, undated, (1 tape)
    - Gluck, Louise at Bennington, 1984, July 24, (1 tape)
    - Gold, Herb at Bennington, 1986, July 18, (1 tape)
    - Green, Ben, undated, (1 tape)
    - Hagy/Nystrom, 1986, April 10, (2 tapes)
    - Hagy, Alyson, 1987, April 21, (1 tape)
    - Hagy, Alyson at Hollins, 1987, April 23, (1 tape)
    - Hagy at University of Virginia, undated, (1 tape)
    - Hall and Bausch at Hollins, undated, (1 tape) (Box AV 5)
    - Halper, Dan, 1981, July 22, (1 tape)
    - Hankla, Cathy at Michigan, 1984, April, 19, (1 tape)
    - Hankla, Cathy and Dillard, R.H.W., 1986, April 27, (2 tapes)
    - Hankla and Dillard, 1987, April 26, (1 tape)
    - Hankla, 1990, Feb. 11, (1 tape)
    - Hansen, Ron, 1983, Dec. 14, and Cheuse and Wier, 1983, Dec. 7, (2 tapes)
    - Hansen, Ron and Jim Shepherd at Michigan, undated, (1 tape)
    - Hardison, O.B. and May Miller at American University, undated, (1 tape)
    - Harrison, William at University of Texas- El Paso, 1979, Aug., (1 tape)
    - Hawkes, John at Bennington, 1982, July 26, (2 tapes)
    - Haxton, Brooks, Douglas, Ellen, 1995, March 11, (1 tape)
    - Hearne, Vickie: Aspen Writers' Conference, 1987, (1 tape)
    - Hearne, Vickie: reading, undated, (1 tape)
    - Hirsch, Ed and Amy Clampitt, 1986, July 22, (2 tapes)
    - Hoffman, Jill at Bennington, 1980, July 8, (1 tape)
    - Hood, Anne, 1986, July 22, (1 tape)
    - Hornberg, Michael and Darcey Steinke, 1995, Feb. 15, (1 tape)
    - Huddle, David at Clark Institute, 1979, Oct. 17, (2 tapes)
    - Humphreys, Josephine, 1987, April 27, (1 tape)
    - Irving, John at Bennington, 1979, July 2, (1 tape)
    - Johnson, Dennis and Paul Nelson, 1983, July 14, (1 tape)
    - Johnson, Dennis, undated, (1 tape)
    - Jones, Kaylie and Jessie Auerbach: First Novels, 1986, July, (1 tape)
    - Katzenbach, Maria and Victor P. (?), undated, (1 tape)
    - Keeley, Edmund, 1986, March 4, (1 tape)
    - Keeley: Part 1, undated, (1 tape)
    - Keeley: Part 2, undated, (1 tape)
    - Kimball, Philip at Bennington, 1980, July 8, (1 tape)
    - Kimball, Philip at University of Virginia, 1984, Oct. 8, (1 tape)
    - Kimball at Johnson State College: Snooker Game, undated, (1 tape)
    - Kimball, Philip at Bennington, undated, (1 tape)
    - Kimball at Johnson State College, undated, (1 tape)
    - Kimball, undated, (6 tapes)
    - Kimball: telling a story and reading from a novel undated, (1 tape)
    - Kinnell, Galway, 1987, July 14, (1 tape)
    - Kinzie, Mary at Michigan, 1984, March, (1 tape)
    - Laidlaw, Brett and Levis, Larry, 1993, March 13, (2 tapes)
    - Landis, James, 1980, July 8, (1 tape)
    - Landis, James, 1981, June 30, (1 tape)
    - LaSalle, Peter and Madison Bell at University of Virginia, 1985, Feb. 10, (2 tapes)
    - LaSalle, Peter at Johnson State College, undated, (1 tape)
    - LaSalle and Roger Rath, undated, (1 tape)
    - LaSalle and Sheila McMillan, n.d, (1 tape)
    - Lavin, Mary: Ploughshares, 1979, Oct. 7, (1 tape)
    - Leithauser, Brad, 1984, March 20, (1 tape)
    - Leonard, John at Bennington, 1984, July 28, (1 tape)
    - Levis, Larry at Hollins, 1993, March 13, (1 tape)
    - Levitas, Brett at University of Virginia, undated, (1 tape)
    - Lewis, William Henry "Hank" at Williams Corner Bookstore, 1995, March 8, (1 tape)
    - Lewis, Hank, 1995, (1 tape)
    - Lewis, Janet: lecture, undated, (1 tape)
    - Lish, Gordon on NPR, 1983, Aug. 4, (1 tape)
    - Longley, Judy, 1989, Feb. 26, (1 tape)
    - Lucas, Anthony, 1983, July 27, (1 tape)
    - Macon, Randolph, 1992, Sept. 30, (1 tape)
    - Madden, David and Robert Drake undated, (1 tape)
    - Mailer, Norman, undated, (1 tape)
    - Maiolo, Joe at University of Virginia, 1988, Nov. 20, (1 tape)
    - Maiolo, Joe at University of Virginia, undated, (1 tape)
    - Masters, Hilary, 1986, March 19, (2 tapes)
    - Matthissen, Peter, undated, (1 tape)
    - Mazzaro, Jerome at Bennington, 1979, Nov. 15, (3 tapes)
    - McCorkle, Jill at University of Virginia, 1984, Nov. 9, (1 tape)
    - McCorkle and Klavans, undated, (1 tape)
    - McDougal, Joe at Stonecoast, 1982, July, (1 tape)
    - McElroy, Colleen, undated, (1 tape)
    - McElroy, Joseph at Stonecoast, 1981, July 21, (1 tape)
    - McGinnis, Joe at Bennington, 1981, July 1, (1 tape)
    - McGinnis, Joe, undated, (2 tapes)
    - McHugh, Heather at Bennington, 1979, July 11, (1 tape)
    - McMillen, Sheila and Alix Shulman at Stonecoast, 1982, July, (1 tape)
    - McMillen and Hagy, 1986, Feb. 13, (2 tapes)
    - McMillen, undated, (1 tape)
    - Merwin, W.S., undated, (1 tape)
    - Mewshaw, Michael, 1987, July 23, (1 tape)
    - 1991, Mewshaw, Mike, 1991, April 28, (1 tape)
    - Mewshaw: interview by Garrett, undated, (1 tape)
    - Mewshaw: conclusion, undated, (1 tape)
    - Milford and Rosenberg at Bennington, undated, (1 tape)
    - Moss, Howard at Bennington, 1982, July 9, (3 tapes)
    - Mueller, Craig and Darcey Steinke, 1986, Nov., (1 tape)
    - Mueller, Craig, undated, (1 tape)
    - Mueller, Lisel and Henry Taylor, 1987, Aug. 3, (1 tape)
    - Mueller, Lisel: reading, undated, (1 tape)
    - Nelson, Kent and David Huddle, 1987, Oct. 11, (1 tape)
    - Nelson, Paul, 1983, July 13, (1 tape)
    - Nichols, Bob and Grace Paley, 1986, July 23, (2 tapes)
    - Nicholson, Jack, undated, (2 tapes)
    - Nicholson, Jack: interview, undated, (1 tape)
    - Nicholson, Jack: part of interview by Alan Cheuse, undated, (1 tape)
    - Nims, John and others, 1991, Jan. 14, (1 tape)
    - Noonan, John, 1978, (1 tape)
    - Noonan, John Ford, undated, (1 tape)
    - Nova, Craig, 1983, July 25, (1 tape)
    - Nystrom, Debra and Sydney Blair, 1991, April 24, (1 tape)
    - Oates, J.C., 1986, April 24, (1 tape)
    - Oates: partial tape, 1986, April 24, (1 tape) (Box AV 6)
    - O'Connor, Tom at University of Virginia, undated, (1 tape)
    - Oles, Carol and Cheuse, Alan, 1988, March 12, (1 tape)
    - Packard, William: poetry class at Wesleyan, 1977, June, (1 tape)
    - Paley, Grace at Johnson State College, 1978, (1 tape)
    - Paley, Grace at Bennington, 1979, July 19, (1 tape)
    - Pieroll, Simon P., undated, (1 tape)
    - Pierson, Mandy, undated, (1 tape)
    - Plumly, Stanley and Madison Bell, 1984, July 25-26, (1 tape)
    - Poster, Carol at Penn State, 1972, July, (1 tape)
    - Poster, Carol at USM, 1979, Sept. 19, (1 tape)
    - Poster, undated, (1 tape)
    - Poster et al., undated, (1 tape)
    - Price, Reynolds: interview with Lynn Ballard, undated, (1 tape)
    - Price, Reynolds: reading from 5 novels, undated, (1 tape)
    - Ramke, Bin: reading, undated, (1 tape)
    - Ramke, Bin: lecture, undated, (1 tape)
    - Rath, Roger, undated, (2 tapes)
    - Rath, Roger and Norton Girault, undated, (1 tape)
    - Robison, Mary and Alan Cheuse, 1987, July 24, (1 tape)
    - Robison and Cheuse, 1987, July 25, (1 tape)
    - Robison and Stephen Dunn, 1986, July 13, (1 tape)
    - Roeser, Dana and Debra Nystrom, 1984, Nov. 15, (1 tape)
    - Rogers, Tim, undated, (1 tape)
    - Rosen, Ken at Johnson State College, undated, (1 tape)
    - Rosen, Ken, undated, (4 tapes)
    - Ruefle, Mary at Bennington, 1979, Oct. 25, (2 tapes)
    - Rurak, Gib at Hollins, 1981, March, (1 tape)
    - Sadoff, Ira at Stonecoast, 1981, July 23, (1 tape)
    - Sadoff, Ira and Andre Dubus, 1983, July 19, (1 tape)
    - Sadoff, at Stonecoast, 1983, July 20, (1 tape)
    - Sadoff, undated, (1 tape)
    - Salter, James, 1991, Feb. 19, (1 tape)
    - Sandy, Stephen at Cambridge, 1979, July, (1 tape)
    - Sandy, Stephen at Johnson State College, 1979, (1 tape)
    - Sandy at Bennington, 1982, July 6, (1 tape)
    - Sandy at Johnson State College, undated, (1 tape)
    - Sandy, undated, (2 tapes)
    - Schwartz, Lynne: lecture, undated, (1 tape)
    - Schwartz, Lynne: reading, undated, (1 tape)
    - Settle, Mary Lee in Blotner's Southern Lit. class at Michigan, 1983, April 5, (1 tape)
    - Settle, Mary Lee: workshop at Michigan, 1983, April 5, (1 tape)
    - Settle, Mary Lee, 1992, March 12, (1 tape)
    - Settle at Michigan, undated, (1 tape)
    - Settle: reading from Strike Night, undated, (3 tapes)
    - Settle, undated, (1 tape)
    - Settle and Janet Burroway at NKU, undated, (2 tapes)
    - Shelnett, Eve, 1975, May 6, (1 tape)
    - Shelnett, Eve, undated, (1 tape)
    - Shrevel, Susan at Hollins, 1985, March 16, (1 tape)
    - Shulman, Alix at Stonecoast, 1983, July 10, (1 tape)
    - Simic, Charles, 1979, July 10, (1 tape)
    - Simic, Charles at Stonecoast, undated, (1 tape)
    - Simpson, Mona and Jay McInerney, 1987, July 16, (1 tape)
    - Slavitt, David at Bennington, 1979, July, (1 tape)
    - Slavitt, David at Bennington, 1980, July 3, (1 tape)
    - Slavitt, at Bennington, 1980, July 4, (1 tape)
    - Slavitt, 1985, April 9, (1 tape)
    - Slavitt, at University of Virginia, 1985, April 9, (1 tape)
    - Slavitt: 50th Book Party, 1994, Oct. 8, (1 tape)
    - Slavitt,: reading poems, undated, (1 tape)
    - Slavitt, and others at York Harbor, undated, (1 tape)
    - Smith, Dave at Bennington, 1983, July 3, (1 tape)
    - Smith, Dave and Nicholas Delbanco, 1983, July 3, (1 tape)
    - Smith, Dave, 1987, Sept. 26, (3 tapes)
    - Smith, Lee at Hollins College, 1981, Feb. 17, (2 tapes)
    - Smith, Lee, 1988, May 16, (1 tape)
    - Smith, Lee at Alabama, undated, (1 tape)
    - Smith, Mark at Bennington, 1982, July, (1 tape)
    - Smith, Mark at University of Virginia, undated, (1 tape)
    - Smith, Ron and Freeman, Ann, 1989, Feb. 5, (1 tape)
    - Snodgrass, W.D. at Bennington, 1979, July, (1 tape)
    - Southwick, Marcia and Ted Conover, 1987, Aug. 6, (1 tape)
    - Southwick, Marcia: lecture, undated, (1 tape)
    - Spires, Elizabeth at Stonecoast, 1981, July 21, (1 tape)
    - Spires, Elizabeth and Madison Bell, 1988, Oct. 9, (1 tape)
    - Spires, 1990, March 17, (1 tape)
    - Spires, undated, (1 tape)
    - Stafford at Michigan, undated, (1 tape)
    - Steinke, Darcey, undated, (1 tape)
    - Strand, Mark at Stonecoast, 1981, July 16, (1 tape)
    - Strand, Mark at Stonecoast, 1982, July 12, (2 tapes)
    - Stuart, Dabney, 1989, April 2, (1 tape)
    - Taylor, Henry and Carolyn Kizer, 1986, Dec. 7, (2 tapes)
    - Taylor, Henry, 1987, June 13, (1 tape)
    - Taylor, Henry and Fred Chappell, 1992, March 7, (1 tape)
    - Taylor, Henry, 1993, Feb. 21, (1 tape)
    - Taylor, Henry at Farmington, 1995, Feb. 9, (1 tape)
    - Taylor, Henry and Carolyn Kizer, undated, (1 tape)
    - Taylor, Henry and Lynn Schwartz, at Aspen, undated, (1 tape)
    - Taylor, Henry: reading, undated, (1 tape)
    - Taylor, Henry: lecture, undated, (1 tape)
    - Taylor, Henry, undated, (2 tapes)
    - Taylor, Henry: on NPR, undated, (1 tape)
    - Taylor, Peter: Hollins Conference, 1970, (1 tape)
    - Tazewell, Widdy, undated, (1 tape)
    - Tillinghast, Richard: reading Sewanee in Ruins, 1984, Feb. 28, (1 tape) (Box AV 7)
    - Tillinghast, Richard at Stonecoast, undated, (1 tape)
    - Townsend, William H., 1953, Oct. 17, (1 tape)
    - Ullman, Leslie at University of Texas- El Paso, 1979, Aug., (1 tape)
    - Ullman, Leslie and Alan Cheuse at Bennington, 1981, July 9, (1 tape)
    - Ullman, and Cheuse, 1982, July, (1 tape)
    - Ullman, 1983, July 7, (1 tape)
    - Vivante, Arthur, 1979, July 13, (1 tape)
    - Voight, Ellen Bryant, undated, (1 tape)
    - Wakoski, Diane, 1984, Jan. 24, (1 tape)
    - Weingarten, Roger, undated, (1 tape)
    - Weiss, Ted at Bennington, 1979, July 27, (1 tape)
    - White, John at Bennington, 1981, July 8, (1 tape)
    - Wier, Allen and Katzenbach, 1979, July 20, (1 tape)
    - Wier, Allen at Bennington, 1982, July 27, (1 tape)
    - Wier, and Bell, Madison at Bennington, 1982, July 27, (1 tape)